[
    {
        "front": "じかん",
        "back": "Time",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    },
    {
        "front": "ごぜん",
        "back": "A.M.",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    },
    {
        "front": "ごご",
        "back": "P.M.",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    },
    {
        "front": "いま",
        "back": "Now",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅっちょう",
        "back": "Business Trip",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    },
    {
        "front": "から",
        "back": "From",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    },
    {
        "front": "まで",
        "back": "Till",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    },
    {
        "front": "いつ",
        "back": "When",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    },
    {
        "front": "たんじょうび",
        "back": "Birthday",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    },
    {
        "front": "せい ねん がっぴ",
        "back": "D.O.B.",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    },
    {
        "front": "なんじ",
        "back": "What Time",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    },
    {
        "front": "なんようび",
        "back": "What Day",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    },
    {
        "front": "なん にち",
        "back": "What Date",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    },
    {
        "front": "おととい",
        "back": "Day before yesterday",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    },
    {
        "front": "きのう",
        "back": "Yesterday",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょう",
        "back": "Today",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    },
    {
        "front": "あした",
        "back": "Tomorrow",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    },
    {
        "front": "あさって",
        "back": "Day after tomorrow",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    },
    {
        "front": "りょこう",
        "back": "Travel, Trip",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    },
    {
        "front": "でした",
        "back": "Past form of des",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    },
    {
        "front": "おしょうがつ",
        "back": "New Year",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    },
    {
        "front": "しけん",
        "back": "Exam",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいもの",
        "back": "Shopping",
        "chapter": "N5 C3"
    }
]